Good morning everyone.
Thank you for joining the call today.
I want to walk through the quarterly results and our plans for the next release.
Thanks for the introduction.
before we start.
Could you share the latest numbers from the marketing campaign?
I am really excited to see them.
Of course.
The campaign reached over 2 million people, and sign-up screw by 40% compared to last quarter.
That is wonderful news.
The team worked very hard on this, and I am proud of what we have accomplished together.
Absolutely.
Now, moving on to the product roadmap, we plan to ship the new dashboard by the end of next month.
great.
I will make sure the documentation is ready before the launch, and we can schedule a demo for the customers.